Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records and Drawings Collection PR 53
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Hotel Syracuse - Syracuse, NY
  - Passenger elevator cab, detail; graphite on trace, 1923-01-15 (Box 320-A)
  - Railings on main staircases to lobby floor, proposed new; graphite on trace, 1924-11-07 (Box 320-A)
  - Soda fountain, revision; graphite on trace, 1923-05-21 (Box 320-A)
  - Plan of platform at revolving doors, cafeteria entrance; graphite on trace, 1923-10-24 (Box 320-A)
  - Diagram of brick coursing btwn 9th fl window head & 10th fl string course; graphite on trace, 1922-11-23 (Box 320-A)
  - Exterior marble work at returns, detail; graphite on trace, 1923-02-19 (Box 320-A)
  - Radiator enclosure on guest room floor; graphite on trace, 1923-11-19 (Box 320-A)
  - Plan thru mantel #639; graphite on trace (Box 320-A)
  - Method of flashing at main roof; graphite on trace, 1922-11-13 (Box 320-A)
  - Location & construction of new dumbwaiter; graphite on trace, fragment missing (Box 320-A)
  - Possible platform treatment in dining room, half-plan; graphite on trace (Box 320-A)
  - Pop-up, waste & ice water combination, typical detail; ink on trace (Box 320-A)
  - Loggia balcony, detail of construction; graphite on trace, 1922-10-31 (Box 320-A)
  - Change of 1st vice president's & secretary's offices, mezz fl.; graphite on trace, 1922-10-30 (Box 320-A)
  - Arrangement of openings for moving picture booth; graphite on trace, 1923-02-13 (Box 320-A)
  - Proposed bathroom on 10th floor; graphite on trace, 1922-12-15 (Box 320-A)
  - Plan of 4 room suite on 7th, 8th & 9th floors, SE corner of building; graphite on trace, 1923-09-12 (Box 320-A)
  - Mezzanine floor details near elevators; graphite on trace, 1924-04-28 (Box 320-A)
  - Show case in beauty parlor; graphite on trace, 1924-04-10 (Box 320-A)
  - Full size sections: jamb, chair rail & head; graphite on trace, 1924-04-01 (Box 320-A)
  - Sink for ice water fountain, cafeteria; graphite on trace, 1924-03-22 (Box 320-A)
  - Elevator lobby, ground floor; graphite on trace, 1923-11-10 (Box 320-A)
  - Plan of screen btwn elevator lobby & dining room; graphite on trace, 1923-11-05 (Box 320-A)
  - Half plan of screen btwn elevator lobby & dining room; graphite on trace, 1923-12-14 (Box 320-A)
  - Screen at NE end of main lobby, relation of base & wainscot; graphite on trace, 1923-10-26 (Box 320-A)
  - Grilles in steel radiator enclosures, main dining room; graphite on trace, 1923-10-18 (Box 320-A)
  - Part elevation of east wall, main dining; graphite on trace, 1923-10-09 (Box 320-A)
  - Telephone booth, f.s. detail; graphite on trace, 1923-09-26 (Box 320-A)
  - Change of officers' toilet to women's toilet, mezzanine floor; graphite on trace, 1924-08-11 (Box 320-A)
  - Women's rest room, booths, etc.; graphite on trace, 1924-07-28 (Box 320-A)
  - Screen partition, banquet kitchen, 10th floor; graphite on trace, 1924-07-23 (Box 320-A)
  - Clothes rack, valet's office; graphite on trace, 1924-06-30 (Box 320-A)
  - Plan of sinkages, main kitchen, 1st floor; graphite on trace, 1924-06-24 (Box 320-A)
  - Detail of telephone booths in main corridor, 10th fl.; graphite on trace, 1924-06-10 (Box 320-A)
  - Marble display; graphite on trace, 1924-06-04 (Box 320-A)
  - Lobby clock in balcony railing; graphite on trace, 1924-06-03 (Box 320-A)
  - 10th floor, additional doors in service hall; graphite on trace, 1924-05-29 (Box 320-A)
  - Details of arch btwn foyer & living room, 9th floor; graphite on trace, 1924-05-15 (Box 320-A)
  - Electric: additional receptacle on 7th, 8th & 9th fl.; graphite on trace, 1924-07-18 (Box 320-A)
  - Heating & electric wiring for display windows, 1st & mezz. floors; graphite on trace, 1924-05-14 (Box 320-A)
  - Chef's office & checkers' desk, main kitchen; graphite on trace, 1924-05-20 (Box 320-A)
  - Telephone room, 1st floor; graphite on trace, 1924-04-09 (Box 320-A)
  - Additional door, office working space, 1st fl.; graphite on trace, 1924-06-16 (Box 320-A)
  - Electric: outlets for future telegraph counter; graphite on trace, 1924-07-17 (Box 320-A)
  - Additional steel covered doors, basement; graphite on trace, 1924-08-07 (Box 320-A)
  - News booth, ground floor; graphite on trace, 1924-06-13 (Box 320-A)
  - Additional bootblack stand, ground floor arcade; graphite on trace, 1924-05-16 (Box 320-A)
- Long Island Historical Society - Brooklyn, NY
  - Mueum floor plan; hectograph & ink wash on paper (Box 350)
  - Attic floor plan; hectograph & ink wash on paper (Box 350)
  - Longitudinal section; hectograph & ink wash on paper (Box 350)
  - Library floor plan; hectograph & ink wash on paper (Box 350)
  - Pierrepont Street elevation; hectograph & ink wash on paper (Box 350)
  - Rear elevation; hectograph & ink wash on paper (minor damage) (Box 350)
  - Lecture room floor plan; hectograph & ink wash on paper (damaged) (Box 350)
  - Transverse section; hectograph & ink wash on paper (Box 350)
  - Clinton Street elevation; hectograph & ink wash on paper (damaged) (Box 350)
  - Half story floor plan; hectograph & ink wash on paper (Box 350)
- Netherlands Building, 1939 World's Fair - New York, NY
  - Main floor mezzanine & basement plan; diazotype on paper (damaged), 1938-10-06 (Box 347)
  - Elevations & sections A-A & B-B; diazotype on paper (damaged), 1938-10-06 (Box 347)
  - Sections C-C, D-D, E-E & F-F; diazotype on paper (damaged), 1938-10-06 (Box 347)
  - Concrete walls, stairs & columns; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1938-09-21 (Box 347)
  - Details of wall sections; blueprint on paper, 1938-06-29 (Box 347)
  - Tower details; blueprint on paper (damaged), 1938-10-25 (Box 347)
  - Niches & expansion joints at exposed exterior columns; blueprint on paper, 1938-07-14 (Box 347)
  - Main floor, mezzanine & basement plan; blueprint on paper, 1938-10-06 (Box 347)
  - Roof plan; blueprint on paper, 1938-10-06 (Box 347)
  - Elevations; blueprint on paper, 1938-10-06 (Box 347)
  - Elevations & sections A-A & B-B; blueprint on paper, 1938-10-06 (Box 347)
  - Sections C-C, D-D, E-E & F-F; blueprint on paper, 1938-10-06 (Box 347)
  - Saw tooth roofs; diazotype on paper, 1938-12-23 (Box 347)
  - Details of approach & ramp; blueprint on paper, 1938-12-14 (Box 347)
  - Details of East India section; blueprint on paper, 1939-01-03 (Box 347)
  - Construction of exterior stairs btwn cols. 1 & 24; blueprint on paper, 1938-12-02 (Box 347)
  - Layout of diorama contour; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1938-07-01 (Box 347)
  - Pump & tank pit under fountain in hall of honor; blueprint on paper, 1939-03-20 (Box 347)
  - Attachment of weather vane to finial & detail of north arrow; blueprint on paper, 1939-03-09 (Box 347)
  - Mullion plan & partition support; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1938-09-29 (Box 347)
  - Structural: mezzanine floor framing plan; blueprint on paper, 1938-08-17 (Box 347-A)
  - Structural: roof framing plan; blueprint on paper, 1938-08-17 (Box 347-A)
  - Structural: column schedule; blueprint on paper, 1938-08-17 (Box 347-A)
  - Structural: roof truss & wind bracing; blueprint on paper (Box 347-A)
  - Structural: roof truss & wall details; blueprint on paper, 1938-08-17 (Box 347-A)
  - Structural: roof truss; blueprint on paper (Box 347-A)
  - Structural: tower; blueprint on paper (Box 347-A)
  - Hall of honor details; blueprint on paper, 1938-10-03 (Box 347-A)
  - Hall of honor details; blueprint on paper, 1938-10-06 (Box 347-A)
  - Plumbing: main floor plan, mezzanine floor & basement toilet rooms; blueprint on paper, 1938-10-25 (Box 347-A)
  - Plumbing: sections & diagrams; blueprint on paper, 1938-10-25 (Box 347-A)
  - Ventilating: basement, main floor & mezzanine exhaust vent; blueprint on paper, 1938-10-25 (Box 347-A)
  - Entrance vestibule foundation & sections; blueprint on paper, 1938-09-24 (Box 347-A)
  - Entrance vestibule foundation & sections; blueprint on paper, 1938-09-22 (Box 347-A)
  - Entrance vestibule ceiling plan & details; blueprint on paper, 1938-09-22 (Box 347-A)
  - Hall of honor glass screens & details; blueprint on paper, 1938-09-29 (Box 347-A)
  - Main, mezzanine & basement plans; blueprint on paper with crayon (damaged), 2 copies (Box 347-A)
  - Structural: truss T4, details; blueprint on paper (Box 347-A)
  - Structural: truss T1, details; blueprint on paper (Box 347-A)
  - Main cornice, exterior f.s. detail; blueprint on paper, 1938-06-29 (Box 347-A)
  - Cornice & cove lighting at portico ceiling; blueprint on paper (Box 347-A)
  - Structural details; blueprint on paper (damaged), 1938-06-29 (Box 347-A)
  - NW & SW elevations; blueprint on paper, 1938-06-29 (Box 347-A)
  - SE & NE elevations, section A-A; blueprint on paper, 1938-06-29 (Box 347-A)
  - Main staircase; blueprint on paper, 1938-06-29 (Box 347-A)
  - Details of rail & baluster (Box 347-A)
  - Foundation plan - concrete grade beams, preliminary; blueprint on paper, 1938-06-29 (Box 347-A)
  - Plan of steel framing, preliminary; blueprint on paper, 1938-06-29 (Box 347-A)
  - Orchestra dias; blueprint on paper, 1939-01-04 (Box 347-B)
  - Diorama floor slab (#1); blueprint on paper, 1939-01-04 (Box 347-B)
  - Location of bolts for attachment of temple sculpture; blueprint on paper, 1939-01-24 (Box 347-B)
  - Mat sinkages in entry vestibule; blueprint on paper, 1938-12-27 (Box 347-B)
  - Extra support for H.A.L. exhibit; blueprint on paper, 1938-12-29 (Box 347-B)
  - Platform for "niveau" relief map machinery; blueprint on paper, 1938-12-15 (Box 347-B)
  - Plan of hall of honor; blueprint on paper (damaged), 1939-01-17 (Box 347-B)
  - Market scene - West Indies room; blueprint on paper, 1938-11-30 (Box 347-B)
  - Switchboard room; blueprint on paper, 1938-12-02 (Box 347-B)
  - Fan support; blueprint on paper, 1938-11-25 (Box 347-B)
  - Window details; blueprint on paper (Box 347-B)
  - Structural: roof truss; blueprint on paper, 1938-09-06 (Box 347-B)
  - Structural: tower; blueprint on paper, 1938-09-06 (Box 347-B)
  - Structural: wall & bracing details; blueprint on paper, 1938-09-06 (Box 347-A)
  - Structural: elevations & sections; blueprint on paper, 1938-09-06 (Box 347-B)
  - Foundation walls & details; blueprint on paper, 6 sheets, 1938-09-14 (Box 347-B)
  - Structural: roof truss and wind bracing; blueprint on paper, 1938-09-06 (Box 347-B)
  - Structural: saw tooth roof truss; blueprint on paper, 1938-09-06 (Box 347-B)
  - Structural: pile cap details; blueprint on paper, 1938-08-26 (Box 347-B)
  - Structural: foundation plan; blueprint on paper, 8 sheets, 1938-09-14 (Box 347-B)
  - Structural: mezzanine floor framing plan; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1938-09-06 (Box 347-B)
  - Structural: roof framing plan; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1938-09-06 (Box 347-B)
  - Structural: column schedule; blueprint on paper, 1938-09-06 (Box 347-B)
  - Structural: anchor bolt location plan; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1938-09-06 (Box 347-B)
  - Garden layout; blueprint on paper, 1938-10-13 (Box 347-B)
  - Steel work drawing list & specification; blueprint on paper (Box 347-B)
  - Concrete door - sub sill; blueprint on paper, 1938-12-12 (Box 347-B)
  - Wood construction details; blueprint on paper, 1938-12-20 (Box 347-B)
  - Detail of wood hand-rail stairs to toilets; blueprint on paper, 1939-04-06 (Box 347-B)
  - East Indies room, interior studding; blueprint on paper, 1939-02-07 (Box 347-B)
  - Field welding on columns & bolts; blueprint on paper, 1938-11-17 (Box 347-B)
  - Catwalk over diorama proscenium; blueprint on paper, 1938-11-22 (Box 347-B)
  - Structural plan [unidentified]; blueprint on paper, 1938-10-27 (Box 347-B)
  - Tower plan & elevation; photostat on paper (Box 347-A)
  - Plan of great hall [Dutch]; photostat on paper, 1938-06-09 (Box 347-A)
  - Plan & walls for Suriname hall [Dutch]; photostat on paper, 1938-06-08 (Box 347-A)
  - Plan for large hall [Dutch]; photostat on paper, 1938-06-09 (Box 347-A)
  - Plan & elevations for display hall [Dutch]; photostat on paper (Box 347-A)
  - Foundation plan; photostat on paper, 1938-06-29 (Box 347-A)
- New York Cotton Exchange - New York, NY
  - Main story: fireplace in smoking room; ink on linen, 1884-03-12 (Box 280)
- New York Produce Exchange - New York, NY
  - Half-story plan; ink on paper backed with linen, damaged, 1885 (Box temp-6)
  - Cellar plan; ink on paper backed with linen, damaged, 1885 (Box temp-6)
  - Main story plan; ink on paper backed with linen, damaged, 1885 (Box temp-6)
  - Third office story plan; ink on paper backed with linen, damaged, 1885 (Box temp-6)
  - First and second office stories plan; ink on paper backed with linen, damaged, 1885 (Box temp-6)
  - First story plan; ink on paper backed with linen, damaged, 1885 (Box temp-6)
  - Section; ink on paper backed with linen, damaged (Box temp-7)
  - Alternate plan of 1st story offices; ink on paper backed with linen, damaged (Box temp-7)
  - East elevation; ink on paper backed with linen, damaged (Box temp-7)
  - End elevations; ink on paper backed with linen, damaged (Box temp-7)
  - Transverse section; ink on paper backed with linen, damaged (Box temp-7)
  - Alternate design for Beaver St. elevation; ink on paper backed with linen, damaged (Box temp-7)
  - End elevations; ink on paper backed with linen, damaged (Box temp-7)
  - Structural: foundation plan; ink on linen, 2 sheets, damaged (Box 341)
  - Structural: main story plan; ink on linen, 3 sheets, damaged (Box 341)
  - Structural: library gallery story plan; ink on linen, damaged (Box 341)
  - Structural: library story plan; ink on linen, damaged (Box 341)
  - Structural: first story plan; ink on linen, 3 sheets, damaged (Box 341)
  - Structural: 1st office story plan; ink on linen, 3 sheets, damaged (Box 341)
  - Structural: 2nd office story plan; ink on linen, 3 sheets, damaged (Box 341)
  - Structural: 3rd office story plan; ink on linen, 3 sheets, damaged (Box 341)
  - Structural: 4th office story plan; ink on linen, 3 sheets, damaged (Box 341-A)
  - Structural: unidentified story part plan; ink on linen, damaged (Box 341-A)
  - Structural: tower plan; graphite on linen, damaged (Box 341-A)
  - Structural: roof plan; ink on linen, 3 sheets, damaged (Box 341-A)
  - Structural: details of trusses; ink on linen (Box 341-A)
  - Structural: trusses from E2 to G2 and E5 to G5; ink on linen (Box 341-A)
  - Structural: truss from N5 to L5; ink on linen (Box 341-A)
  - First story, large office at NE corner of building, plan showing furring & flues; ink on linen, 1883-02-09 (Box 341-A)
  - Cellar plans, 1st story coping, tower windows; graphite on linen (damaged) (Box 341)
  - Structural: plan giving templates for roof girders, the red figures are from the bottom of the 4th office story beams to bottom of girders; ink on linen (Box 341)
  - Main room, part of north end; ink on linen (Box 341-A)
  - First tower story, elevator shafts; ink on linen (Box 341-A)
  - Plan of parapet wall and coping, sections I, II & III; ink on linen, 3 sheets (Box 341-A)
  - Structural: basement plans sections 1-3; ink on linen, 3 sheets (Box 341-A)
  - Structural: 3rd office story plans, sections 1-3; ink on linen, 3 sheets, 1882-12-28 (Box 341-A)
  - Structural: 2nd office story plans, sections 1-3; ink on linen, 3 sheets, 1882-11-20 (Box 341-A)
  - Structural: 1st office story plans, sections 1-3; ink on linen, 3 sheets, 1882-11-21 (Box 341-A)
  - Structural: 1st story plans, sections 1 & 2; ink on linen, 2 sheets (Box 280)
  - Structural: main story plans, sections 2 & 3; ink on linen, 2 sheets, 1882-06-21 (Box 280)
  - 1st story plan showing furring, flues, etc., sections 1 & 3; ink on linen, 2 sheets (Box 280)
  - Heat & vent: elevation of wall on New Street showing flues, etc.; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Heat & vent: elevation of wall on Broadway & Whitehall Street showing flues, etc.; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Part exterior elevation; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Part plan of basement showing possible changes; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Design for elevator cars: sections & plans; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Plan of call room; ink on linen, 1884-01-16 (Box 280)
  - Tower: section through archway; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Floor plan showing gas outlets; ink on linen, 1883-10-31 (Box 280)
  - Skylight in main room showing daylight openings; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - 3rd & 4th office stories: plans & elevations; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Transoms under stairs: mezzanine & 1st office story; ink on linen, 1883-10-13 (Box 280)
  - Plan of the Pennsylvania R.R. offices; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Gallery (balcony) for main room; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Section through centre of call room & elevation of centre beam; ink on linen, 1884-01-05 (Box 280)
  - Basement columns of tower elevators; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Diagram of vault; ink on linen, 1883-09-20 (Box 280)
  - Ceiling arch in library; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Library: elevation of south end; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Library: elevation of gallery; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Library: elevation of west side; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Library: elevation of north end; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - 1st story Beaver St. staircase: bronze hand-rail for brackets; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Tower: gate in passage btwn piers L8 & L9; ink on linen, 1884-01-25 (Box 280)
  - Position of hydraulic passenger elevators, Stone St. side; ink on linen, 1883-02-20 (Box 280)
  - Position of hydraulic passenger elevators, Beaver St. side; ink on linen, 1883-02-20 (Box 280)
  - Library floor: plan of plates and plaster partitions; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Plan & elevation of pier M7 & N7; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Roof or 1st tower story plan; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Stair in 1st story hall, Safe Deposit Company; ink on linen, 1883-10-19 (Box 280)
  - Basement story: inside elevation of north tower wall; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Dining room: transverse section; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Library: iron railings for upper & lower gallery; ink on linen, 1883-12-12 (Box 280)
  - Copper balustrade in cornice; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Entrance door transom & dome light, Safe Deposit Co.; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - North tower: eight blue stone sills; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Plan of vault, Safe Deposit Co.; ink on linen, 1883-09-20 (Box 280)
  - Brick vault, pier P3 & P4, plan & elevation, NY Safe Deposit Co.; ink on linen, 1884-02-21 (Box 280)
  - Unidentified plan; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - 1st tower story: west elevation; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Tower: section & south elevation showing section of roof & 1st tower story windows; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - North wall court, columns of the skylight; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Unidentified single story exterior elevation; ink on linen (Box 280)
  - Boiler room; graphite on trace (damaged) (Box 280-A)
  - Boiler room; graphite on trace, 1883-10-06 (Box 280-A)
  - Unidentified diagram & sketches; graphite on trace (damaged) (Box 280-A)
  - Boiler rooms plan (Babcock & Wilcox); graphite on trace (Box 280-A)
  - Structural plan showing lighting (roof?); graphite on trace (damaged) (Box 280-A)
  - Boiler room; graphite on trace (damaged) (Box 280-A)
  - Boiler room plan (?); graphite on trace (damaged) (Box 280-A)
  - Door to NY Safe Deposit Co., entering from 1st story hall; graphite on trace (damaged), 1884-02-09 (Box 280-A)
  - North elevation of house on tower; aniline on paper (Box 280-A)
  - Cellar & 1st story: iron work between piers 07 & 08; aniline on paper (damaged, folded) (Box 280-A)
  - Main staircases: elevations, detail of posts; aniline on paper (damaged), 1884-02-08 (Box 280-A)
  - Sills in tower above main roof; ink on paper (damaged) (Box 280-A)
  - Boiler room plan; blueprint on paper (Box 280-A)
  - Detail of SW corner of skylight; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box 280-A)
  - Plan of ceiling under skylight & part plan of roof of skylight; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box 280-A)
  - Hydraulic passenger elevators: Stone St. side plans; blueprint on paper (Box 280-A)
  - Basement columns of tower elevators; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box 280-A)
  - Proposed alterations: main floor plan; graphite on trace (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: section on line C-D; graphite on trace (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 2nd intermediate floor plan; graphite on trace (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: section on line A-B; graphite on trace (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: beam plan for 1st & 2nd floors; graphite on trace (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 1st intermediate floor plan; graphite on trace (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: sketch showing columns & beam connections; graphite on trace, 1906-12-26 (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 2nd intermediate floor part plans; graphite on trace, 2 sheets (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: block elevation; graphite on trace, 1936-02-26 (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 1st floor plan; ink & graphite on trace (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 2nd floor plan; ink & graphite on trace, 1936-02-26 (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 3rd, 4th & 5th floor plan; ink & graphite on trace, 1936-02-26 (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 6th-13th floor plan; ink & graphite on trace, 1936-02-26 (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 14th-21st floor plan; ink & graphite on trace (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 22nd floor, typical tower plan; ink & graphite on trace, 1936-02-26 (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: setbacks on 3 streets; graphite on trace, 1936-03-20 (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 2nd, 3rd & 4th floor plans; graphite on trace, 1936-03-20 (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 5th-12th floor plans; graphite on trace, 1936-03-20 (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 13th-16th floor plans; graphite on trace, 1936-03-20 (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 17th-22nd floor plans; graphite on trace, 1936-03-20 (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: ground floor plan; graphite on trace, 1936-03-20 (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: 1st floor plan; graphite on trace, 1936-03-20 (Box 188)
  - 4th office story, office arrangements; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - Projected roof story; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - 4th office story, club arrangement; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - Foundation plan [?]; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - Basement plan; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - Main floor plan; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - Library stories plans; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - 3rd office story plan; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - 4th office story, office arrangements; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - Library story & gallery plans; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - 1st story plan; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - Basement plan; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - 2nd office story; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - Main story plan; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - 1st office story; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - 4th office story plan; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - Basement plan showing drainage; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - 2nd office story plan; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - 1st office story plan; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - Intermediate & tower story plans; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - 3rd office story plan; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - Tower stories; ink on linen (Box 188)
  - Sketches for Banker's Trust Co. floor plans; graphite on trace, 2 sheets (Box 188)
  - Correspondence re: alterations to building; 2 typewritten sheets & copy of same, 1906-12-26 (Box 188)
  - Proposed alterations: block elevation; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1936-02-26 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations: 1st floor plan; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1936-02-26 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations: 2nd floor plan; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1936-02-26 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations: 3rd-5th floor plan; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1936-02-26 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations: 6th-13th floor plan; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1936-02-26 (Box 188-A)
  - Proposed alterations: 14th-21st floor plan; blueprint on paper, 2 copies, 1936-02-26 (Box 188-A)